A Guide to the Rockefeller foundation records, projects, SG 1.16-1.19 (A90-A93) FA469
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.16-1.19 (A90-A93)
1978-1993
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation
FA469
292.71 Cubic Feet
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Project files transferred to the RAC by Rockefeller Foundation, 1990-1993.
Arrangement note
Records are arranged as received. Within folders, materials are primarily arranged in reverse chronological order.
RG 1.16 is arranged by the Rockefeller Foundation traditional series (country code) and subseries (program letter) structure.
Subsequent subgroups are arranged by program, with RG 1.17 being the most prominent transition period where some materials are arrranged by the outgoing traditional series/subseries, and others are arranged by program.
Conditions Governing Access note
Records more than 20 years old are open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. RAC is unable to provide access to obsolete media and original digital media. In addition separated media may not yet have undergone stabilization procedures. When feasible, a digital surrogate may be created via special order. All applicable charges will apply.
Scope and Contents
Types of records include: projects files and related material.
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A90), 1980-1988; 1.16; 32.56 Cubic Feet; 74 letter size document storage boxes (Boxes 1-74)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
  Arrangement
  Arranged by the Rockefeller Foundation series (country code or series number) and subseries (program letter) structure.
  Records are arranged as received. Within folders, materials are primarily arranged in reverse chronological order.
  - International Potato Program (IPP), 107
    - International Potato Center (CIP) - Angelique Haugerud (107), 1979-1988 (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
    - International Potato Center (CIP) - Angelique Haugerud (107), 1979-1988 (Box 1, Folder 1A)
      Restricted - Confidential material
  - International Irrigation Management Institute (IIMI), 108
    - International Irrigation Management Institute (108), 1982-1990 (Box 1, Folder 4-5, Box 2, Folder 6-7)
      General
      Grant numbers AS 8311 and AS 8421
    - International Irrigation Management Institute - David Groenfeldt (108), 1982-1987 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - International Irrigation Management Institute - David Groenfeldt (108), 1982-1987 (Box 2, Folder 8A)
  - International Center of Tropical Agriculture (CIAT), 110
    - International Center of Tropical Agriculture (110), 1983-1990 (Box 2, Folder 9-10, Box 3, Folder 11-12)
      International Center of Tropical Agriculture: Centro Internacional de Agricultura Tropical (CIAT)
      Folder 12 - Supplementary Material
    - International Center of Tropical Agriculture - Scott E. Guggenheim (110), 1983-1988 (Box 3, Folder 13-14, Box 4, Folder 15-16)
      Folder 13A - Closed Material - Medical and personal information; Folders 14-16 - Supplementary Material
    - International Center of Tropical Agriculture - Scott E. Guggenheim (110), 1983-1988 (Box 3, Folder 13A)
    - International Center of Tropical Agriculture - Steven Romanoff (110), 1984-1988 (Box 4, Folder 17-19)
    - International Center of Tropical Agriculture - Steven Romanoff (110), 1984-1988 (Box 4, Folder 17A)
    - International Center of Tropical Agriculture - Joachim Voss (110), 1982-1987 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - International Center of Tropical Agriculture - Joachim Voss (110), 1982-1987 (Box 5, Folder 20A)
  - International Laboratory for Research on Animal Diseases (ILRAD), 112
    - International Laboratory for Research on Animal Diseases - Theileriosis Immunization Workshop (112), 1983-1985 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - International Livestock Centre for Africa (ILCA), 113
    - International Livestock Centre for Africa - Irene T. Whalen (113), 1981-1985, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - International Livestock Centre for Africa - Irene T. Whalen (113), 1981-1985, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 22A)
  - International Institute of Tropical Agriculture (IITA), 115
    - International Institute of Tropical Agriculture - Paul Dorosh, 1984-1988, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 23, Box 6, Folder 24)
    - International Institute of Tropical Agriculture - Paul Dorosh, 1984-1988,1990 (Box 6, Folder 23A)
  - International Crops Research Institute for the Semi-Arid Tropics (ICRISAT), 116
    - International Crops Research Institute for the Semi-Arid Tropics - Karen Dvořák (116), 1983-1988 (Box 6, Folder 25-26)
    - International Crops Research Institute for the Semi-Arid Tropics - Karen Dvořák (116), 1983-1988 (Box 6, Folder 25A)
  - The International Centre of Insect Physiology and Ecology (ICIPE), 117
    - The International Centre of Insect Physiology and Ecology - W. Thomas Conelly (117), 1982-1988 (Box 6, Folder 27, Box 7, Folder 28)
    - The International Centre of Insect Physiology and Ecology - W. Thomas Conelly (117), 1982-1988 (Box 6, Folder 27A)
  - International Center for Agricultural Research in the Dry Areas (ICARDA), 118
    - International Center for Agricultural Research in the Dry Areas - Dennis Tully (118), 1982-1989 (Box 7, Folder 29-31)
      Folder 29A - Closed Material - Medical and personal information
    - International Center for Agricultural Research in the Dry Areas - Dennis Tully (118), 1982-1989 (Box 7, Folder 29A)
  - International Agricultural Development Service (IADS), 119
    - International Agricultural Development Service - China Agriculture Meeting (119), 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - International Agricultural Development Service - Project Proposal (119), 1983 (Box 8, Folder 33)
      Project proposal to allow IADS, Virginia State University, and Tuskegee Institute to prepare a proposal for technical assistance to the Government of Senegal
    - International Agricultural Development Service - Review Team (119), 1981 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120
    - Agricultural Research Priorities - Conference (120), 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 35-38, Box 9, Folder 39-40)
      Bellagio Conference, "Allocating Resources for Developing Country Agricultural Research"
      Folders 38-40 - Supplementary Material
    - American Literature in Multi-National Perspectives - Conference (120), 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Apomixis in Crop Improvement - Conference (120), 1985-1988, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 42-44)
      Bellagio Conference - "The Potential Use of Apomixis in Crop Improvement"
    - Comparative Political Finance and Political Corruption - Conference (120), 1985-1987, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Developing Policies for Responding to Climatic Change - Conference (120), 1986-1988 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Economic Policy in Closed and Open Economies - Conference (120), 1984-1986 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Economics and Elections: Western Europe and the United States (120), 1985-1987, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Emerging Nuclear Suppliers and Nonproliferation - Conference (120), 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Intra-Household Processes and Farming Systems Analysis - Conference (120), 1982-1987 (Box 10, Box 50-51)
    - Future of the International Steel Industry, II - Conference (120), 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Future Strategies for the Consultative Group on International Agricultural Research (CGIAR) - Conference, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 53-54)
    - Gender, Technology and Education - Conference (120), 1984-1988 (Box 11, Folder 55-57, Box 12, Folder 58-59)
    - Genetically-designed Organisms in the Environment - Conference (120), 1986-1988, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - History of Public Health Education - Conference (120), 1985-1989 (Box 12, Folder 61)
    - Intergovernmental Politics and Social Policymaking - Conference (120), 1984-1986, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 62)
    - International Institute of Comparative Government - Conference (120), 1985-1987 (Box 12, Folder 63)
    - International Productivity Comparisons - Conference (120), 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 64)
    - International Relations of East Asia in the Eisenhower Era - Conference (120), 1986-1987, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 65)
    - Intersectoral Cooperation: A Paradigm for Health Development - Conference (120), 1985-1986, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 66)
    - Literature and Ideology in the Slavic World - Conference (120), 1985-1987 (Box 13, Folder 67)
    - Management of Transboundary Groundwater - Conference (120), 1985-1988 (Box 13, Folder 68)
    - Molecular Pharmacology of Protozoan Parasites - Conference (120), 1984-1986 (Box 13, Folder 69)
    - Ownership, Management and Editors of the Media - Conference (120), 1985-1988, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 70)
    - Performing Arts in Europe and America - Conference (120), 1984-1987 (Box 13, Folder 71-72, Box 14, Folder 73-77)
      Folders 75-77 - Supplementary Material
    - Performing Arts in Europe and America - Conference - Tape 1 (120), circa1983-1987; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1, Tape AV 9957)
      Scope and Contents
      Intro - June 10; A.M. - June 11
      Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact an archivist for further details.
    - Performing Arts in Europe and America - Conference - Tape 2 (120), circa 1983-1987; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1, Tape AV 9958)
      A.M. - June 11; A.M. - June 11
    - Performing Arts in Europe and America - Conference - Tape 3 (120), circa 1983-1987; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1, Tape AV 9959)
      June 11 - A.M.; June 11 - A.M. and P.M.
    - Performing Arts in Europe and America - Conference - Tape 4 (120), circa 1983-1987; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1, Tape AV 9960)
      June 11 - P.M.; June 11 - P.M.
    - Performing Arts in Europe and America - Conference - Tape 5 (120), 1983-1987; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1, Tape AV 9961)
      June 11 - P.M., June 12 - A.M.; June 12 - A.M.
    - Performing Arts in Europe and America - Conference - Tape 6 (120), circa 1983-1987; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1, Tape AV 9962)
      June 12 - A.M.; June 12-13 - A.M.s
    - Performing Arts in Europe and America - Conference - Tape 7 (120), circa 1983-1987; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1, Tape AV 9963)
      June 13 - A.M.; June 13 - A.M.
    - Performing Arts in Europe and America - Conference - Tape 8 (120), circa 1983-1987; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1, Tape AV 9964)
      June 13 - A.M.; June 13 - A.M.-P.M.
    - Performing Arts in Europe and America - Conference - Tape 9 (120), circa 1983-1987; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1, Tape AV 9965)
      June 13 - P.M.; June 13 - P.M.
    - Performing Arts in Europe and America - Conference - Tape 10 (120), circa 1983-1987; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1, Tape AV 9966)
      June 13 - P.M.
    - Priority Health Problems in Curriculum Development - Conference (120), 1984-1987 (Box 15, Folder 78-79)
    - Reconstruction of Europe's Bombed Cities - Conference (120), 1986-1987, 1989, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 80)
    - Refugees in the Islamic World - Conference (120), 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 81)
    - Scholars - Abramovitz, Moses (120), 1985-1987, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 82)
    - Scholars - Al-Khal, Yusuf (120), 1985-1987 (Box 16, Folder 83)
      Did not go
    - Scholars - Altschul, Carlos (120), 1985-1986, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 84)
    - Scholars - Anderson, Donald S. (120), 1987-1989 (Box 16, Folder 85)
    - Scholars - Anderson, Roy M. (120), 1985-1986, 1988, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 86)
    - Scholars - Benedek, Elissa P. (120), 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 87)
    - Scholars - Black, Douglas (120), 1985-1988 (Box 16, Folder 88)
    - Scholars - Blum, Eva M. Spitz (120), 1987-1989 (Box 16, Folder 89)
    - Scholars - Bowden, Ann (120), 1985-1986, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 90)
      With husband William B. Todd
    - Scholars - Bradbury, Malcolm (120), 1986-1987, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 91)
    - Scholars - Braudy, Leo (120), 1985-1987, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 92)
    - Scholars - Bronkhorst, Johannes (120), 1986-1987, 1989-1990, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 93)
    - Scholars - Brown, Rosellen (120), 1985-1987, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 94)
    - Scholars - Brushwood, John S. (120), 1985, 1987-1989 (Box 17, Folder 95)
    - Scholars - Butler, Ruth (120), 1986-1987, 1992, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 96)
    - Scholars - Carl, Robert (120), 1986-1992, 1995-1996, 1998-1999 (Box 17, Folder 97)
    - Scholars - Castex, Mariano N. (120), 1985-1986, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 98)
    - Scholars - Chalmers, Iain (120), 1986-1987, 1989, 1991, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 99)
      Worked with Murray W. Enkin and Marc J. N. C. Keirse
    - Scholars- Cheang, Molly (120), 1985-1989 (Box 17, Folder 100)
    - Scholars - Collins, Robert O. (120), 1979, 1985-1987. 1990, 1992, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 101)
    - Scholars - Condé, Maryse (120), 1986-1989, 1995, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 102)
    - Scholars- Cook, Albert (120), 1988-1989, 1992, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 103)
    - Scholars - Cortés, Josefina R. (120), 1986-1988 (Box 18, Folder 104)
    - Scholars - Craton, Michael J. (120), 1986-1988 (Box 18, Folder 105)
    - Scholars - Cripps, Thomas (120), 1984-1988, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 106)
    - Scholars - Crowder, Michael (120), 1985-1988 (Box 18, Folder 107)
    - Scholars - Crowder, Michael (120), 1985-1988 (Box 18, Folder 107A)
    - Scholars - Daly, Martin W. (120), 1986-1991 (Box 18, Folder 108)
    - Scholars - Dhandayudham, R. (120), 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 109)
    - Scholars - Dillon, Millicent G. (120), 1985-1988, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 110)
    - Scholars - Dittrich, Paul-Heinz (120), 1981, 1986-1988, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 111)
    - Scholars - Drexler, Rosalyn (120), 1984-1988, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 112)
    - Scholars - Durand, Régis (120), 1985-1988 (Box 18, Folder 113)
    - Scholars - Dworkin, Gerald (120), 1986-1987, 1998, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 114)
    - Scholars - Eitner, Lorenz (120), 1984-1988 (Box 18, Folder 115)
    - Scholars - Evans, L. T. (120), 1984-1987, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 116)
    - Scholars - Exner, Richard (120), 1984-1989, 1991, 1992, 1995-1996 (Box 18, Folder 117)
    - Scholars - Falk, Avner (120), 1986-1987, 1989, 1993, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 118)
    - Scholars - Fausto, Boris (120), 1986-1989, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 119)
    - Scholars - Feldman, Gerald D. (120), 1986-1988, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 120)
    - Scholars - Fisher, Humphrey John (120), 1986-1989 (Box 19, Folder 121)
    - Scholars - Fitterer, John A. (120), 1985-1988 (Box 19, Folder 122)
    - Scholars - Fuchs, Victor R. (120), 1986-1988 (Box 19, Folder 123)
    - Scholars - Goldman, Michael (120), 1985-1988 (Box 19, Folder 124)
    - Scholars - Goodman, Howard C. (120), 1985-1987 (Box 19, Folder 125)
    - Scholars - Greene, Naomi (120), 1986-1987, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 126)
    - Scholars - Griliches, Zvi (120), 1985-1988, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 127)
    - Scholars - Guerrero, Rodrigo (120), 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 128)
    - Scholars - Hagstrum, Jean H. (120), 1986-1987,1992 (Box 19, Folder 129)
    - Scholars - Hall, James W. (120), 1984-1988, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 130)
    - Scholars - Hamilton, Charles V. and Dona C. (120), 1984-1988, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 131)
    - Scholars - Haskell, Molly (120), 1986-1987, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 132)
    - Scholars - Hayward, Jack E. S. (120), 1985-1986, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 133)
    - Scholars - Hick, John (120), 1985-1986, 1988-1989 (Box 20, Folder 134)
    - Scholars - Hoagland, Edward M. (120), 1986-1987, 1989, 1993, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 135)
    - Scholars - Hobson, J. Allan (120), 1986-1988, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 136)
    - Scholars - Holl, Karl (120), 1986-1989, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 137)
    - Scholars - Hollander, John (120), 1985-1989, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 138)
    - Scholars - Hollander, Robert (120), 1986-1987, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 139)
    - Scholars - Hrachovec, Herbert (120), 1986-1987, 1989, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 140)
    - Scholars - Humphrey, Nene (120), 1985-1989, 1992, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 141)
      Co-resident - Benny Andrews
    - Scholars - Kamal, Daud (120), 1985-1988, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 142)
    - Scholars - Kartun-Blum, Ruth (120), 1985-1987 (Box 21, Folder 143)
    - Scholars - Kilroy, Thomas (120), 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 144)
    - Scholars - Kleinman, Arthur (120), 1985-1987 (Box 21, Folder 145)
    - Scholars - Langbaum, Robert (120), 1985-1987 (Box 21, Folder 146)
    - Scholars - Laslett, Barbara (120), 1985-1987 (Box 21, Folder 147)
    - Scholars - Lifshitz, Fima (120), 1985-1988, 1991, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 148)
    - Scholars - Lipa, Jerzy J. (120), 1984-1988 (Box 21, Folder 149)
    - Scholars - Lope-Blanch, Juan M. (120), 1986-1990 (Box 21, Folder 150)
    - Scholars - Lopez, Salvador P. (120), 1984-1989 (Box 21, Folder 151)
    - Scholars - Lotringer, Sylvère (120), 1985-1988 (Box 21, Folder 152)
    - Scholars - Lurie, Alison (120), 1986-1988, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 153)
    - Scholars - McCord, William M. (120), 1985-1986, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 154)
    - Scholars - Mahakun, Vicha (120), 1985-1987, 1989-1990 (Box 22, Folder 155)
    - Scholars - Mahapatra, Jayanta (120), 1985-1991 (Box 22, Folder 156)
    - Scholars - Mark, Joan (120), 1985-1986, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 157)
    - Scholars - Marshall, Ingram (120), 1986-1989, 1994, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 158)
    - Scholars - Miller, Joseph C. (120), 1984-1989 (Box 22, Folder 159)
      Working with Dr. Zhen-Zhuan Luo
    - Scholars - Miller, James E. III (120), 1985-1987 (Box 22, Folder 160)
    - Scholars - Moss, Lawrence (120), 1985-1986, 1989, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 161)
    - Scholars - Napier, A. David (120), 1982-1984, 1986, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 162)
    - Scholars - Nickel, John L. (120), 1986-1989, 1996, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 163)
    - Scholars - Nipperdey, Thomas (120), 1985-1987, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 164)
    - Scholars - Oakley, Ann Rosamund (120), 1986-1988, 1990, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 165)
    - Scholars - O'Connell, Jeffrey (120), 1985-1991, 1997, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 166)
    - Scholars - Okolo, Julius Emeka (120), 1985-1989, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 167)
    - Scholars - Olson, Toby (120), 1986-1987, 1990, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 168)
    - Scholars - Paulson, Ronald (120), 1986-1987, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 169)
    - Scholars - Pieniążek, Szczepan A. (120), 1986-1987, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 170)
    - Scholars - Potts, Malcolm (120), 1984-1986, 1988, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 171)
      Working with Winfield Best and Roger V. Short
    - Scholars - Putnam, Robert D. (120), 1986-1988, 1991, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 172)
    - Scholars - Pylant-Backus, Carol (120), 1985-1987, 1989-1990, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 173)
    - Scholars - Reiser, Morton F. (120), 1985-1987, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 174)
    - Scholars - Reuss-Ianni, Elizabeth and Ianni, Francis A. J. (120), 1985-1987, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 175)
    - Scholars - Rodis-Lewis, Genevieve (120), 1985-1986, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 176)
    - Scholars - Rose, Peter I. (120), 1985-1987, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 177)
    - Scholars - Ross, George (120), 1985-1987, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 178)
    - Scholars - Rubenstein, Carol P. (120), 1986-1988 (Box 24, Folder 179)
    - Scholars - Schulman, Grace (120), 1985-1989, 1992, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 180)
    - Scholars - Shemin, David (120), 1986-1989 (Box 24, Folder 181)
    - Scholars - Shklar, Judith N. (120), 1985-1986, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 182)
    - Scholars - Siegel, Roberta S. (120), 1985-1990, 1996, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 183)
    - Scholars - Silverman, Faye-Ellen (120), 1986-1988, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 184)
    - Scholars - Stern, Leo (120), 1985-1987 (Box 25, Folder 185)
    - Scholars - Summers, Anita A. (120), 1985-1987, 1996, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 186)
    - Scholars - Summers, Robert (120), 1985-1986, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 187)
    - Scholars - Syme, S. Leonard (120), 1986-1988 (Box 25, Folder 188)
    - Scholars - Syme, Ronald (120), 1986-1989 (Box 25, Folder 189)
    - Scholars - Syme, Ronald (120), 1986-1989 (Box 25, Folder 189A)
    - Scholars - Tilakasiri, Jayadeva (120), 1985-1986, 1988, 1991, 2005, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 190)
    - Scholars - Trachtenberg, Alan (120), 1986-1989 (Box 25, Folder 191)
    - Scholars - Tsuzuki, Chushichi (120), 1986-1987, 1990-1991, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 192)
    - Scholars - Tunley, David (120), 1985-1988, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 193)
    - Scholars - Vendler, Helen (120), 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 194)
    - Scholars - Vendryes, Georges (120), 1985-1987 (Box 25, Folder 195)
    - Scholars - Vigée, Claude (120), 1985-1989 (Box 26, Folder 196)
    - Scholars - Watt, Ian (120), 1985-1987 (Box 26, Folder 197)
    - Scholars - Weissmann, Gerald (120), 1986-1988, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 198)
    - Scholars - Wightman, David R. (120), 1984-1986, 1988, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 199)
    - Scholars - Wilcox, Donald J. (120), 1984-1986, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 200)
    - Scholars - Wortman, Richard (120), 1985-1987, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 201)
    - Soviet International Behavior - Conference (120), 1984-1986 (Box 26, Folder 202-204, Box 27, Folder 205-208, Box 28, Folder 209-211)
      Folders 206-211 - Supplementary Material
      Conference title - Soviet Foreign Policy in an Uncertain World
    - State and Social Regulation in Italy - Conference (120), 1985-1986 (Box 28, Folder 212)
    - Technology and Development - Conference (120), 1986-1988 (Box 28, Folder 213)
    - Trade Policy in Developing Countries - Conference (120), 1986-1987, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 214)
    - U.S.-Soviet Competition and the Issue of Alignment and Non-Alignment - Conference (120), 1985-1987 (Box 29, Folder 215)
      Conference title - U.S.-Soviet Competition and the Issue of Alignment and Non-Alignment: Prospects for the 1990s
    - War and Society in East Central Europe - Conference (120), 1984-1986 (Box 29, Folder 216)
      Conference title - War and Society in East Central Europe: Civilian and War Leaders from the 18th to the 20th Century
    - Women In and After War - Conference (120), 1985-1988 (Box 29, Folder 217)
    - Women "in Dark Times" - Conference (120), 1985-1987 (Box 30, Folder 218)
  - 140
    - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 140E
      - Nyong'o., Peter Anyang', 1982, 1984-1987 (Box 30, Folder 219)
      - Boonprasat-Lewis, Nantawan, 1983-1986 (Box 30, Folder 220)
      - Budiman, Arief, 1983-1986, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 221)
      - Ekeh, Peter P., 1983-1987 (Box 30, Folder 222)
      - Ghee, Lim Teck, 1983-1988 (Box 31, Folder 223)
      - Ileto, Reynaldo C., 1983-1986 (Box 31, Folder 224)
      - Luckham, Y. F. Yeboah (Yaa), 1983-1986 (Box 31, Folder 225)
      - Mamdami, Mahmood, 1983-1987 (Box 31, Folder 226)
      - Mangahas, Mahar, 1983-1987 (Box 32, Folder 227)
      - Mehretu, Assefa, 1983-1986, 1988-1989 (Box 32, Folder 228-231)
      - Milimo, Mabel C., 1984-1987 (Box 33, Folder 232)
      - Mnthali, Felix, 1983-1987 (Box 33, Folder 233)
      - Muzaffar, Chandra, 1983-1986, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 234-235, Box 34, Folder 236)
      - Suksamran, Somboon, 1983-1986 (Box 34, Folder 237-238)
      - Wongtrangan, Kanok, 1983-1986 (Box 34, Folder 239)
  - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy, 150
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Ford Administered - Julie DaVanzo, 1981-1983 (Box 34, Folder 240)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Ford Administered - John F. Kantner, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 241)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Ford Administered - Ray Langston, 1981-1984 (Box 35, Folder 242)